[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High, Linda becomes pregnant.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Good Friday Earthquake, which occurred on March 27, 1964, is the most powerful earthquake in U.S. history. It killed approximately 13,000 people.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following countries is the worlds smallest continent, and can also be considered an island since it is surrounded by water?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Africa", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Paul Newman portray in the 1961 movie The Hustler?", "correct_answer": "Pool player", "incorrect_answers": ["Bowling player", "Baseball player", "Chess player"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this language, jo reggelt means good morning and Beszel angolul means Do you speak English?", "correct_answer": "Hungarian", "incorrect_answers": ["Romanian", "Russian", "Croatian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What should one do on examination day in order not to chase away good luck according to Russian superstition?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["One should not cut their nails.", "One should not wear anything new.", "One should not make their bed."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Home Alone, what is the name of Kevins neighbor, the elderly man, who is allegedly a murderer called The South Bend Shovel Slayer?", "correct_answer": "Marley", "incorrect_answers": ["Ziggy", "Bob", "Carlyle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only UN member not allowed to be on the Security Council?", "correct_answer": "Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["The Congo", "Vietnam", "Sudan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of Henry VIII\u2019s wives outlived him?", "correct_answer": "Catharine Parr", "incorrect_answers": ["Catharine of Aragon", "Anne Boleyn", "Jane Seymour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What novel by Russian writer Leo Tolstoy opens with this often quoted line: Happy families are all alike; every unhappy family is unhappy in its own way.?", "correct_answer": "Anna Karenina", "incorrect_answers": ["War and Peace", "Doctor Zhivago", "Crime and Punishment"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was The Exorcist released?", "correct_answer": "1973", "incorrect_answers": ["1971", "1972", "1970"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the expression Kai yat sai, denoting a Thai omelette?", "correct_answer": "Stuffed eggs", "incorrect_answers": ["Sun and snow", "Spicy eggs", "Eggs and cheese"]}]